<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArticleInfo>

    <Description
        id="2"
        title="The Worst Advice for Entrepreneurs"
        category="Finance"
        text="How do you know who do listen to?
When you decide to start a new business, everyone from your spouse, your mother, your friends, even your mailman, has an opinion. If you bring up your new entrepreneurial pursuits at dinner you will get a flood of advice about things you should or shouldn’t do. Don’t get me started about what happens when you turn to Google for help.

Some of this advice will be helpful and some will not. But no matter what, I guarantee you that you’ll be overwhelmed by the number of opinions you get. It’s your job to sort out the good advice from the bad, a task that is more difficult than it seems. How do you tell the good from the bad?
When trying to determine if the advice you’re receiving is good or bad, it’s best to start by looking at who is giving you the advice and what their purpose is for giving it to you.

Start by looking at who is giving you the advice. Does this person have experience doing what you want to do? Do they know what they’re talking about? Do their actions match their words?

Just because your Uncle Bob talks a big game, doesn’t mean he has the expertise to back it up. But, your neighbor who you never knew ran a successful Amazon store, might be a great person to listen to.

Some common bad advice
Don’t do it”

The most common form of advice is to simply not do it. Everyone will have this advice in the beginning, particularly if it’s your first business or if you’re leaving your steady paycheck job to pursue it.

This advice comes in all shapes and forms. They will tell you horror stories of people who tried and failed to start businesses. They will remind you of the many reasons you should stay in your “safe” job and not risk your money and time.

Even seasoned entrepreneurs still get this advice. Robert and I often hear people telling us not to take risks, expand into new investments, or grow certain parts of our company. But we’ve learned over time to tune them out and do what we feel is right.

Unless your business involves jumping out of a plane without a parachute, don’t listen to this advice. Don’t let other people’s insecurities and doubts hold you back from changing your life for the better.

“Be Like This Business/Person”

Everyone is going to want to compare your business to another. Even you might fall into that trap when describing your new venture. Comparisons can be useful, as long as they don’t hold you back from building a business that works for you.

Your business should be unique to your values, goals, and priorities. There are some great business models out there that can be starting points when you’re outlining your structure. But don’t try to copy and paste their business plan exactly.

Use your creativity and build a business that’s yours, and no one else’s. And when people try to tell you to do things like someone else, remind them that you are your own person.

“Go back to school first”

This was Robert’s poor dad’s favorite piece of advice. His father was an educator, and he believed that Robert should go back to school, get his MBA, maybe even his PhD. A lot of people will tell you that you should get your MBA before starting a business.

There’s nothing wrong with going back to school. A lot of people find value in getting another degree. But let’s be clear: You don’t need an MBA or a college degree to start a business.

Some of the most successful entrepreneurs of our time were college, even high school dropouts. I’m not advocating that you follow their example (again, you are your own person). But don’t listen to the advice that you have to go back to school or get this or that degree before you can start a successful business.


The only advice that matters
There is so much advice out there when you’re starting your business. This can be comforting, and provide you with great ideas and direction. It can also be overwhelming, because many times the advice you receive contradicts itself.

That’s why, at the end of the day, the only person you really need to listen to is yourself. Listen to advice, collect opinions, thank people for their words, and then do what you want to do. That’s how successful entrepreneurs are made.

Source: Kim Kiosaki, Richdad Advisors" />

</ArticleInfo>